export const allQuestions = [
  {
    question: "Which type of JavaScript language is?",
    answers: {
      a: "Object-Oriented",
      b: "Object-Based",
      c: "Assembly Language",
      d: "High-level"
    },
    correctAnswer: "b"
  },
    {
      question: "Who invented JavaScript?",
      answers: {
        a: "Douglas Crockford",
        b: "Sheryl Sandberg",
        c: "Brendan Eich",
        d: "Ravi Teja"
      },
      correctAnswer: "c"
    },
    {
      question: "Which is not a form of client-side storage?",
      answers: {
        a: "Web Databases",
        b: "FileSystem API",
        c: "Offline Web Apps",
        d: "Online Web Apps"
      },
      correctAnswer: "d"
    },
    {
      question: "Which object supports Filesystem API?",
      answers: {
        a: "Element",
        b: "File",
        c: "Window",
        d: "DOM"
      },
      correctAnswer: "b"
    },
    {
      question: "The localStorage and sessionStorage belongs to?",
      answers: {
        a: "Window Object",
        b: "Element Object",
        c: "Hash Object",
        d: "DOM Object"
      },
      correctAnswer: "a"
    },
    {
      question: "What is the main difference between localStorage and sessionStorage?",
      answers: {
        a: "Lifetime",
        b: "Scope",
        c: "Both Lifetime and Scope",
        d: "Storage Location"
      },
      correctAnswer: "c"
    },
    {
      question: "What is the lifetime of the data stored through localStorage?",
      answers: {
        a: "Permanent",
        b: "Temporary",
        c: "Both Permanent and Temporary",
        d: "Cannot store"
      },
      correctAnswer: "a"
    },
    {
      question: "Which one of these is a JavaScript package manager?",
      answers: {
        a: "Node.js",
        b: "TypeScript",
        c: "npm",
        d: "nvm"
      },
      correctAnswer: "c"
    },
    {
      question: "Which tool can you use to ensure code quality?",
      answers: {
        a: "Angular",
        b: "jQuery",
        c: "RequireJS",
        d: "ESLint"
      },
      correctAnswer: "d"
    },
    {
      question: "Which tool can you use to ensure code quality?",
      answers: {
        a: "Angular",
        b: "jQuery",
        c: "RequireJS",
        d: "ESLint"
      },
      correctAnswer: "d"
    },
  ];